<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!--
  ~ /*
  ~ Copyright (c) 2013 Wes Lanning, http://codingcreation.com
  ~
  ~ Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining
  ~ a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the
  ~ "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including
  ~ without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish,
  ~ distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to
  ~ permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to
  ~ the following conditions:
  ~
  ~ The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be
  ~ included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
  ~
  ~ THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
  ~ EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF
  ~ MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND
  ~ NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE
  ~ LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION
  ~ OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION
  ~ WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
  ~
  ~ http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php
  ~ */
  -->

<resources>
    <!-- **************** Dialog related stuff **************** -->

    <!-- ====== Strings related to showing the additional info area warning dialog ====== -->

    <string name="warningDialogTitle">Continuez avec Soin! Ici, il ya Dragons.</string>
    <string name="warningDialogText">Les paramètres sur l\'écran suivant sont normalement cachés des utilisateurs. Une mauvaise configuration de ces paramètres peut perturber votre connexion réseau. En cas de doute, ne plaisante pas avec eux ou sauvegarde de votre appareil.
    </string>
    <string name="dialogNoPromptTxt">J\'ai ete prevenu des consequences possibles si je bousille ces preferences.  Je promis que je ne ferais aucun des choses suivantes: \n\nBlamer au promoteur. \n\nDonner un mauvais commentaire. \n\nFaire du promoteur mon soutien technique personal. ☺
    </string>

    <!-- ====== Messages shown if the user cannot access the additional setting area ====== -->

    <string name="noSupportDialogTitle">Device Locked</string>

    <string name="noAdditionalSettingSupport"><![CDATA[Your device manufacturer (probably Samsung) decided to lock down your device model beyond what Google recommends by default. Unfortunately that means I cannot include access to the network settings shortcut for users without root and rooted devices with SELinux restrictions. \n\nSome rooted devices (probably Samsung once again) running Android 5.0 (Lollipop) or later are additionally locked out due to SELinux restrictions that cannot be bypassed without a custom or modified kernel. For example, if other rooted apps work on your device, but you cannot access this shortcut in my app, then your device is locked down by an SELinux policy that won\'t let non-system apps (like mine) launch system app activities such as the network settings shortcut. \n\nI do not currently own any Samsung devices and cannot help you directly with rooting. Instead, please find your device\'s forum on xda-developers.com for more information. \n\nIf functionality like switching the network type is important to you, I would recommend not buying devices from this manufacturer in the future, no matter how nice their devices might be.]]>
    </string>

    <!-- **************** /End Dialog related stuff **************** -->
</resources>